[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[knocking on door]
[敲门声]
- Ooh, they're here.
哦，他们来了。
- Who's ready for our boys only sleepover?
谁准备好迎接我们的男生专属睡衣派对？
all: Yeah!
耶！
[knocking on door]
[敲门声]
- Who's ready for our girls only sleepover?
谁准备好迎接我们的女生专属睡衣派对？
all: Yeah!
耶！
- This sleepover's gonna be awesome!
这个睡衣派对一定会很棒！
- Finally a night with just us dudes, no girls.
终于一个晚上只有我们这些家伙，没有女生。
all: No girls!
没有女生！
- This sleepover's gonna be so much fun.
这次睡衣派对一定会很有趣。
- Finally, a night with just us ladies, no boys.
终于，一个只有我们女士的夜晚，没有男生。
all: No...
没有...
boys?
男生？
all: Girls?
女生？
all: Mom!
妈妈！
- Tom! - Anne.
汤姆！ - 安妮。
all: Dad? - Oh!
爸爸？ - 哦！
Oh, hey, hey. Hey, everybody. What's going on?
哦，嘿，嘿。嘿，大家好。发生什么事了？
- Uh, Tom, by any chance did you tell the boys
呃，汤姆，你有没有可能告诉男孩们
that they could have their sleepover
他们可以在女孩们举行聚会的同一天
on the same night as the girls?
也来个睡衣派对？
- Anne, please. I'm a grown man.
- 安妮，拜托。我是个成年人了。
I think I know how to schedule things.
我想我知道怎么安排事情。
Dawn, when did I say you could have yours?
道恩，我什么时候同意你们今晚举行的？
- Tonight.
- 今晚。
- And boys?
- 男孩们呢？
all: Tonight.
大家：今晚。
- I see.
- 我明白了。
- Tom, when are you going to admit
汤姆，你什么时候才会承认
that your mental calendar does not work,
你的大脑日历不管用，
and you're gonna have to start writing things down?
你得开始记下事情了？
- I mixed up one little thing. Why are you so dolled up?
我就搞错了一件事。你为什么打扮得这么隆重？
- Uh, you also scheduled our date night for tonight.
呃，你还把我们的约会夜定在今晚了。
- Oh, I'm just kidding. Heh. I'm dressed.
哦，我开玩笑的。嘿。我穿好了。
I'm just...Boulder cas'.
我只是...穿了博尔德的。
- Yeah, those are my sweatpants.
是啊，那是我的运动裤。
- I see.
我明白了。
- I wish we could unsee.
我希望我们能视而不见。
- Can we please get back to the sleepover problem?
我们能回到过夜派对的问题上吗？
We can't all stay in the same house.
我们不能都住在同一个房子里。
- Ooh, I'd like to make a case for the boys,
哦，我想为男孩们说句话，
since we need all of this room
因为我们需要所有这些空间
to play our virtual reality wrestling game.
来玩我们的虚拟现实摔跤游戏。
- Yeah, we put on goggles and gloves,
是的，我们戴上眼镜和手套，
and it's like we're actually in the video game.
就好像我们真的在电子游戏里一样。
- It's pretty cool.
这很酷。
- Sounds like the cool part's virtual too.
听起来酷的部分也是虚拟的。
- It's cool, okay?
很酷，好吗？
- Well, we have plans too. So who gets to stay?
- 嗯，我们也有计划。所以谁留下来？
- There's a perfectly mature way to settle this.
- 有一个完全成熟的方式来解决这个问题。
First one to say dibs! boys: Dibs!
第一个说‘我要了’的！男孩们：我要了！
- Boom. - Yes!
- 砰。 - 是的！
- Dibs? Seriously?
- 我要了？认真的？
- Let's not waste any more time. We can just go to my house.
- 我们不要再浪费时间了。我们可以直接去我家。
- Perfect. There definitely won't be any boys there.
- 完美。那里肯定不会有男孩。
Why are we still seeing boys?
我们为什么还在看到男孩？
- Sorry, just let me say bye.
- 对不起，让我先说再见。
- Bye, Miles.
- 再见，迈尔斯。
- Bye, Mae.
再见，梅。
- You hang up first.
你先挂电话。
- No, you hang up.
不，你先挂。
- No, you. - No, you.
both: No, me!
不，我先挂！
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[upbeat rock music]
♪ 欢快的摇滚音乐 ♪
- Whoa!
哇！
[both grunting]
（两人哼哼声）
- Got him! The Dentist is down!
抓到他了！牙医倒下了！
- Now it's time to put Big Bad Baby Boy to bed.
现在是时候让大坏宝贝男孩睡觉了。
It's nap time. - [grunting]
该午睡了。 - （哼哼声）
Baby Boy needs a bottle!
宝贝男孩需要一个奶瓶！
- Yes! We are the Three Mask-eteers,
是的！我们是三面具斗士，
the terrible teenagers of wrestling.
摔跤界的可怕青少年。
- I'm Stop. - I'm Drop.
- 我是Stop。 - 我是Drop。
- I'm Roll.
- 我是Roll。
all: We're on fire!
我们火力全开！
- Yeah, I don't see it.
- 是啊，我没看出来。
- But I do see a perfect dude night ahead.
- 但我看到了一个完美的兄弟之夜。
VR wrestling, and then we get to go to a real match later?
虚拟现实摔跤，然后我们晚点还能去看真正的比赛？
- You know, I wonder what the girls are doing.
- 你知道，我在想女孩们现在在干什么。
- Pbbf, probably something lame and girly.
- 哼，大概是在做些无聊又女孩子气的事吧。
- Give me the offset ratchet driver
- 给我那个偏置棘轮扳手
with the carbon Phillips head bit, stat.
带碳钢菲利普斯头螺丝刀，快点。
- Flyin' in.
- 飞进来。
- Debbie's going to love this. Aren't you, Debbie-Boo-Boo?
- 黛比会喜欢这个的。对吧，黛比宝贝？
I could just eat your cute little paws.
我真想咬一口你那可爱的小爪子。
And a one paw, and a two paw...
一爪，两爪...
- Mae, if there's a three paw, we will literally
- 梅，如果有三爪，我们马上停止建造。
stop building this right now.
- 对不起，我只是太爱她了！
- Sorry, but I just love her so much!
- 不知道男生们在干什么。
- I wonder what the boys are doing.
- 蠢、汗、吵、臭的男生事。
- Dumb, sweaty, noisy, smelly boy stuff.
还能有什么？
What else? [all laugh]
[大家都笑了]
- Hand me the princess-cut ruby with the diamond inlay, stat!
- 快，把那个镶有钻石的公主切割红宝石递给我！
And it is done.
完成了。
This championship belt will be awarded to the winner
这条冠军腰带将颁发给
of our VR wrestling tournament.
我们VR摔跤比赛的获胜者。
May the best man win!
愿最强的男人获胜！
Heavy, heavy...too many gems.
太重了...宝石太多了。
[thud]
[砰]
- I can't believe we're gonna get to see the real Dentist
- 真不敢相信我们今晚能看到真正的牙医
and Big Bad Baby Boy tonight.
和坏坏宝贝男孩。
- And the real Three Mask-eteers.
- 还有真正的三面具侠。
- [strained] A little help?
- [费力] 帮把手？
- I gotta show this to Mae.
- 我得给梅看看这个。
- Hey, no more video chats with Mae.
- 嘿，别再和梅视频聊天了。
It's dude night.
今晚是哥们之夜。
- I'm just gonna send her a quick pic.
- 我就给她发张快照。
- Fine, just one.
- 好吧，就一张。
[camera shutter clicks]
[相机快门声]
- OMG. They're ridiculous.
- 天哪。他们太离谱了。
- [laughing] Yes, they are.
- [笑] 没错，他们是。
No more boys.
别再提那些男孩了。
- I can't believe any of them would think they could be
我真不敢相信他们中有人会认为自己能成为
actual pro wrestlers.
真正的职业摔跤手。
- Especially Miles. He couldn't even hurt a spider,
尤其是迈尔斯。他连一只蜘蛛都伤害不了，
never mind win a championship belt.
更别提赢得冠军腰带了。
He's just a big ol' softy. [all laugh]
他只是一个大软心肠的家伙。[大家都笑了]
[phone chimes] - Voicemail sent.
[手机响了] - 语音信箱已发送。
- Uh-oh.
- 哎呀。
- Oh, no!
- 哦，不！
You just butt-dialed Miles and left a message!
你刚刚不小心给迈尔斯拨了电话并留了言！
- Uh, well, don't worry. You didn't say anything bad.
- 呃，别担心。你没说什么不好的话。
- Are you kidding? I know Miles,
- 你在开玩笑吗？我了解迈尔斯，
and me calling him a big ol' softy
我叫他大软心，
will definitely hurt his feelings.
肯定会伤到他的感情。
- Really? - Yes!
- 真的吗？ - 是的！
Because he's a big ol' softy!
因为他就是个大软心！
- Okay, okay, look, I'll just call the boys,
- 好吧，好吧，听着，我这就打电话给那些家伙，
and have them delete the message on Miles' phone
让他们在迈尔斯听到之前删除他手机上的信息。没问题的。
before he can even listen to it. No problemo.
[男孩们哼哼唧唧，手机震动]
[boys grunting, phone vibrating]
- [叹气] 那些家伙都没接电话。
- [sighs] None of the boys are picking up.
- 他们肯定是在玩游戏。
They must be in the middle of their game.
他们一定是在玩游戏。
- No problemo, huh?
没问题，是吧？
- Wait, hold on. That's a good thing.
等等，等等。这是个好事。
Since they're in the middle of their game,
既然他们在玩游戏，
it gives me time to go home, sneak in,
这给了我时间回家，悄悄进去，
and delete the message without them seeing me.
在他们没看见我的情况下删除消息。
Problemo solvo...d.
问题解决了...
- You should sneak in through the doggie door
你应该从狗门偷偷进去
and crawl into the living room.
然后爬进客厅。
- Then pin 'em to the ground
然后把他们按在地上
and do something to their face!
然后对他们的脸做点什么！
- Or I could just use my key.
- 或者我可以用我的钥匙。
- Good idea!
- 好主意！
Poke their face with a key!
用钥匙戳他们的脸！
- Yeah, let's hold that as a backup plan.
- 是的，让我们把这个作为备用计划。
♪ ♪
- Anne, I figured out how to make it up to you
- 安妮，我想到了如何弥补忘记我们的约会之夜。
for forgetting our date night.
我要为你做一顿充满心意、自制的浪漫晚餐。
I am going to cook you
a heartfelt, homemade, romantic dinner.
- That's so sweet, Tom.
- 汤姆，你真贴心。
- Do we have any Beefaroni in the freezer?
- 冰箱里还有牛肉通心粉吗？
- Romantic, Tom.
- 真浪漫，汤姆。
- Oh, you know what would be romantic?
- 哦，你知道什么才浪漫吗？
- Not having mini-bagel pizzas?
- 不是迷你百吉饼披萨吗？
- No.
- 不是。
Finally sharing a piece of our wedding cake.
- 终于分享我们的婚礼蛋糕了。
- I'm sorry, Tom, but I'm off cake.
- 对不起，汤姆，我不吃蛋糕了。
Ever since your mother sent us that awful anniversary cake...
- 自从你妈妈送了我们那个糟糕的周年纪念蛋糕之后……
[gagging] I can't eat cake.
- [作呕] 我吃不下蛋糕了。
- It's our wedding cake.
- 这是我们的婚礼蛋糕。
It was made with love and chocolate ganache.
它是由爱和巧克力甘纳许制成的。
- I don't know, it's been in there 15 years.
- 我不知道，它已经在那里放了15年。
I mean, are you sure it's still good?
我是说，你确定它还能吃吗？
- Ah, of course, Anne.
- 啊，当然，安妮。
Have I ever been wrong about anyth...
我什么时候错过过任何事...
It has ganache.
它有甘纳许。
- Now, Dentist! Do the face crusher!
- 现在，牙医！做面部粉碎者！
- I thought we were doing the face stomper!
- 我以为我们要做面部践踏者！
- Just do something to their face!
- 就对他们的脸做点什么吧！
[boys grunting]
[男孩们发出哼声]
- Ugh, locked.
- 呃，锁住了。
[phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
Miles' phone is locked. Do you know the password?
迈尔斯的手机锁住了。你知道密码吗？
- No. But he loves my cat,
- 不知道。但他喜欢我的猫，
so try, "I love Debbie."
所以试试，“我爱黛比。”
- No, nothing.
- 不行，没用。
- Then he probably uses his fingerprint.
- 那他可能用的是指纹解锁。
- His fingerprint? - Is that a problemo?
- 指纹？ - 有问题吗？
- No, no, no, no problemo.
- 不，不，不，没问题。
[chuckles nervously]
[紧张地轻笑]
[groans]
[呻吟]
[boys grunting]
[男孩们哼哼]
[gasps]
[喘气]
Big problemo.
大问题。
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
- What are you do--
- 你在做什么——
- Shh.
- 嘘。
- Help! [grunting]
- 救命！[哼哼]
- Sorry, but there's an embarrassing message
- 对不起，但迈尔斯手机上有梅发来的尴尬信息
from Mae on Miles' phone, and I need you to help me
来自Mae在Miles手机上的信息，我需要你帮我
get his fingerprint so I can unlock it and erase it.
获取他的指纹，这样我就可以解锁并删除它。
- You know this is dude night, so why should I help you?
- 你知道今晚是哥们之夜，我为什么要帮你？
- Because I'm your sister.
- 因为我是你妹妹。
- Yes, but you're still not a dude.
- 是的，但你还是不是个哥们。
- Yeah, well Miles is your friend; he's a dude.
- 对，但Miles是你的朋友；他是哥们。
- But you're still not! - Listen, dude!
- 但你还是不是！- 听着，哥们！
If Miles hears that message,
如果Miles听到那条信息，
he's gonna get really bummed out
他会非常沮丧
and ruin your beloved dude night.
并且毁了你珍爱的哥们之夜。
- Oh, well you should've led with that.
哦，那你应该一开始就说的。
I don't want anything to ruin dude night.
我可不想任何事情毁了哥们之夜。
Now if you'll kindly lower your key,
现在请你把钥匙放低，
I'll go put him in a virtual Mask-eteer drop, and...
我去把他放进虚拟的蒙面骑士投放中，然后...
you do whatever you gotta do.
你做你该做的事。
- Okay. [boys grunting]
好的。
- I've got you in a virtual Mask-eteer drop, Dentist!
我已经把你放进虚拟的蒙面骑士投放了，牙医！
Now it's time for you to open up and say, "Ah!"
现在是你张开嘴说‘啊’的时候了！
[both grunting]
（两人哼哼声）
- [grunting]
（哼哼声）
- Dudes are so weird.
伙计们真是奇怪。
[sniffing] And smelly.
还臭烘烘的。
[phone chirps]
Yes! Got it!
太好了！搞定了！
- Yes! I am the champion!
太棒了！我是冠军！
- [gasps] both: Dawn?
- I am virtual.
我是虚拟的。
- What was Dawn-- - Who was that--
刚才那个是Dawn吗？
[both grunting]
- What's going on? - Why was Dawn here?
发生什么事了？Dawn为什么在这儿？
- She said-- - It's dude night.
- 她说-- - 今晚是哥们之夜。
She can't be here. - Yes, but she said--
她不能在这里。 - 是的，但她说了--
- There are time-honored traditions
- 有些传统
that must be followed. - Like the freedom
必须遵守。 - 比如在后院上厕所的自由。
to use the backyard as a bathroom.
- 你们俩谁有钥匙？
- Either of you have a key?
- 哦，我总是带着我的日记钥匙。
- Ooh, I always have my journal key.
- 谢谢。
- Thanks.
现在听着！
Now listen!
道恩来这里是为了删除一条消息
Dawn came over here to delete a message
梅不小心留在迈尔斯手机上的消息
that Mae accidentally left on Miles' phone
Mae不小心留在Miles手机上的
that would've hurt his feelings
那会伤害他的感情
and ruined dude night.
并毁了哥们之夜。
- [sighs] Well, that's good,
（叹气）好吧，那挺好，
because we wouldn't want anything
因为我们不想有任何事情
to ruin that wrestling match for us.
毁了那场摔跤比赛。
- You have a journal?
你有日记？
- Whoo!
哇哦！
Ooh, feeling the pain
哦，在那个残忍的虚拟炸弹摔之后
after the vicious virtual piledriver
感觉到了疼痛
I laid on you?
我压在你身上了？
- No, Mae's cat Debbie scratched me
- 不，是Mae的猫Debbie抓了我
when I tried to pet her yesterday.
昨天我试图抚摸她的时候。
I do not like that cat!
我不喜欢那只猫！
- Not a word about this to Miles.
- 关于这件事不要对Miles说一个字。
- Definitely not! - Yeah.
- 绝对不要！ - 是的。
we all know how Miles feels about Mae.
我们都知道Miles对Mae的感觉。
- I mean, I pretend to like her, but I'm living a lie.
- 我是说，我假装喜欢她，但我其实是在撒谎。
And, you know, I can't tell Mae, 'cause I know
而且，你知道，我不能告诉Mae，因为我知道
she'd be devastated if she knew I didn't like her at all.
如果她知道我根本不喜欢她，她会非常伤心的。
- Really? Dude, this is huge.
真的吗？伙计，这可是大事。
- This is huge. Miles doesn't like Mae.
这可是大事。Miles不喜欢Mae。
- What were you guys just doing in the closet?
你们俩刚才在衣橱里做什么？
- Uh...well, when you think about it,
呃...好吧，你想想看，
what are any of us doing anywhere?
我们任何人在任何地方都在做什么呢？
Will you excuse us?
你能让我们单独待会儿吗？
- Well, that was a bombshell.
哇，那可是个重磅炸弹。
- I know. Ricky just made me question our entire existence.
我知道。Ricky刚刚让我对我们整个存在产生了疑问。
- No, not that. About Mae.
不，不是那个。是关于Mae的。
What do you guys think we should do?
你们觉得我们应该怎么办？
- Well, I'll tell you
好吧，我告诉你
one thing we shouldn't do:
有一件事我们不应该做：
handle it ourselves.
自己处理这件事。
- That's right. - We're terrible handlers.
没错。 - 我们处理得糟透了。
- Oh, maybe we should call Dawn.
哦，也许我们应该叫Dawn来。
She'll know how to handle it. - Oh.
她会知道怎么处理的。 - 哦。
[phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
- Ugh, boys!
唉，男孩们！
[ringing continues]
[铃声继续]
[groans] What's up?
[呻吟]怎么了？
The closet? Why?
衣柜？为什么？
Oh, uh... [chuckles nervously]
哦，呃... [紧张地笑]
Eeh...
呃...
Nicky thinks he left his, uh...
Nicky觉得他把他的，呃...
...corduroy cargo shorts in the garage closet.
...灯芯绒工装短裤落在车库的衣柜里了。
[chuckles]
[笑]
Excuse me. [chuckles]
不好意思。[笑]
Okay, I'm alone. What's up?
好吧，我现在一个人。怎么了？
- Wait, before we go any further,
- 等等，在我们继续之前，
who wears corduroy cargo shorts?
谁会穿灯芯绒工装短裤？
- Mostly boat owners and men of leisure.
- 主要是船主和闲散男士。
- Okay, can we forget about the shorts?
- 好吧，我们能不谈短裤了吗？
What's going on?
发生什么事了？
- There's a problem with Mae and Miles.
- Mae和Miles之间有问题。
- Yeah, we've got trouble in paradise.
- 是的，我们的天堂出了点问题。
- What does that mean?
- 那是什么意思？
- It usually indicates when a couple is having trouble--
- 这通常表示一对夫妻遇到了麻烦——
- Okay, I know what it means, but what does it mean ?
- 好吧，我知道那是什么意思，但具体是什么意思？
- We just overheard Miles tell Dooley
- 我们刚巧听到Miles向Dooley坦白了他对Mae的真实感受。
how he really feels about Mae.
就是这样，可以说情况并不那么美好。
- Yeah, and let's just say it wasn't so paradise-y.
是的，这么说吧，情况并不那么美好。
- Why are you telling me this?
你为什么要告诉我这个？
Now I have no choice but to tell Mae.
现在我别无选择，只能告诉Mae。
She's my best friend. - Well, our other option
她是我的好朋友。
was handling it ourselves.
我们还有一个选择是自己处理。
- You made the right choice.
你做出了正确的选择。
Did Miles say anything else,
Miles还说了别的什么吗，比如他为什么会有这种感觉？
like why he's feeling this way?
嗯，我们并没有完全听到整个对话。
- Well, we didn't exactly hear the whole conversation.
好吧，我没有更多信息的话，就不能告诉Mae。
- Okay, well I can't tell Mae unless I have more information.
我需要你们弄清楚为什么天堂会有麻烦。你们能处理这个吗？
I need you guys to figure out why there's trouble in paradise.
我需要你们弄清楚为什么天堂里会有麻烦。
Can you handle that? - If we were good handlers,
你们能处理吗？ - 如果我们是好的处理者，
we wouldn't have called you in the first place.
我们一开始就不会叫你来了。
- Just handle it!
- 处理好它！
- Hey, Miley-mi, random question.
- 嘿，Miley-mi，随便问个问题。
Not prompted by anything at all.
绝对不是因为任何事情。
Earlier, when you said you don't like her,
之前，当你说你不喜欢她时，
exactly why don't you like her?
具体为什么你不喜欢她？
- Well, I don't want this getting back to Mae.
- 嗯，我不想这事传到Mae耳朵里。
You know, you promise you won't tell?
你知道，你保证不会告诉别人？
- No, of course not. - Promise.
- 不，当然不会。 - 我保证。
- Bro code.
- 兄弟守则。
- She's just so moody, you know?
- 她就是太情绪化了，你知道吗？
Sometimes I'm talking to her, and she just walks away
有时候我跟她说话，她突然就走开
to stare at birds out the window.
去盯着窗外的小鸟看。
- She does? - That's weird.
- 她会这样？ - 这有点奇怪。
- Ooh, a blue jay!
- 哦，一只蓝松鸦！
- Truthfully, it makes me not even want
- 说实话，这让我甚至不想
to be around her anymore.
再待在她身边了。
- Will you excuse us again? We're just gonna...yeah.
- 能再让我们单独待会儿吗？我们只是想...对。
- Where have you guys been? This closet's hot!
你们去哪儿了？这衣橱里热死了！
- You've been in the closet the whole time?
你一直都在衣橱里？
- I mean, I ducked out for a minute,
我是说，我出去了一会儿，
but there were too many questions
但关于那条工装短裤的问题太多了，所以我回来了。
about the cargo shorts, so I came back in.
那你们还发现了什么？
So what else did you find out?
比我们想的还要糟糕！
- It's worse than we thought!
是啊，迈尔斯甚至不想再靠近梅。
- Yeah, Miles doesn't even want to be around Mae at all.
一点儿都不想？
- "At all" at all?
[静电声]
[static crackling]
Like they're spending too much time together?
就像他们在一起时间太长了吗？
[crackling continues] - What? We can't hear you.
什么？我们听不见你。
You're breaking up!
你的信号断了！
- Did you just say they're gonna break up?
你刚才是说他们要分手吗？
- Did she just say they're breaking up?
她刚才是说他们在分手吗？
- I can't believe Mae's going to break up with Miles!
我不敢相信Mae要和Miles分手！
- I can't believe Miles is gonna break up with Mae!
我不敢相信Miles要和Mae分手！
- I can't believe we ate all this cake!
我不敢相信我们吃了这么多蛋糕！
all: This is bad!
这太糟糕了！
- [whistling]
吹口哨
- I got it. - You got a signal?
- 我明白了。 - 你收到信号了？
- No, I know why they call it a selfie.
- 不，我知道他们为什么叫它自拍。
Because you take it with your cell phone.
因为你用手机拍。
- No, it's because you take it of yourself.
- 不，是因为你拍的是自己。
- That would be a your-fie. [scoffs]
- 那应该是你的自拍照。[嗤之以鼻]
Doofy.
傻乎乎的。
- Poor Miles.
- 可怜的Miles。
I wonder when Mae is going to kick him to the curb.
我想知道Mae什么时候会甩了他。
- Probably next time she sees him,
- 可能下次她见到他的时候，
so we should tell him before we go to the match tonight.
所以我们应该在今晚去看比赛前告诉他。
- No, we can't!
- 不行，我们不能告诉他！
If we tell him, he'll be bummed out
如果我们告诉他，他会因为
about Mae breaking up with him,
梅要和他分手而心情低落，
and it'll ruin dude night.
那样就会毁了我们的哥们之夜。
- Yeah, what good friends would do is not tell him
- 对啊，好朋友应该是在哥们之夜后才告诉他
until after dude night.
而不是之前。
- So we should be good friends and leave for the match now
- 所以我们现在应该作为好朋友，出发去看比赛，
so that Mae can dump him after dude night's done.
让梅在哥们之夜结束后再和他分手。
- Miles is lucky to have us.
- 迈尔斯有我们这样的朋友真是幸运。
- We're really good dudes.
- 我们真的是很棒的哥们。
- I told you! There's 27 coats in there!
- 我告诉过你了！里面有27件外套！
- Psh, whatever.
- 随便啦。
- They argue about the weirdest stuff.
- 他们争论的东西真是奇怪。
- Well, fellas, we should head out.
- 好了，伙计们，我们该出发了。
- We still have a lot of time.
- 我们还有很多时间。
- Not as much as you think.
- 没有你想象的那么多。
- Mom! Dad! Can you take us
- 妈妈！爸爸！现在能带我们去摔跤比赛吗？
to the wrestling match now?
- 呃！我觉得我们蛋糕吃太多了，安妮！
- Ugh! I think we ate too much cake, Anne!
- 我觉得它变质了，汤姆。15年太久了！
- I think it turned, Tom. 15 years is too long!
- 那我们怎么去比赛呢？
- Well, how do we get to the match?
好吧，我们怎么去比赛现场？
- Cab!
打车！
- We don't have enough money for a cab!
我们没有足够的钱打车！
- [gagging] Bus!
（作呕声）公交车！
- [whistling]
（吹口哨）
- Nice work.
干得好。
This is gonna be perfect for Deb--
这对Deb来说太完美了——
What the heck?
搞什么鬼？
- Sorry, it's just that I have some bad news.
对不起，只是我有一些坏消息。
My brothers told me that there's trouble in paradise.
我兄弟们告诉我，天堂出问题了。
- Miles is breaking up with me?
- Miles要和我分手？
- Wow, I was really hoping the whole trouble in paradise thing
- 哇，我原本真的希望那个'天堂里的麻烦'的事情
would kind of ease us into it, but yes.
能让我们慢慢适应，但确实如此。
- Why?
- 为什么？
- See, I'm not sure.
- 这个，我不确定。
All I know is the boys overheard Miles telling Dooley
我只知道我兄弟们无意中听到Miles告诉Dooley
that he doesn't want to be around you anymore.
说他不想再和你在一起了。
- Doesn't want to be around me?
- 不想和我在一起？
I am delightful! - Yes, you are!
我可是很讨人喜欢的！ - 没错，你是！
- And as cute as a basket of kittens!
- 而且可爱得像一篮子小猫！
- Even cuter!
- 甚至更可爱！
- If Miles doesn't want to be around me,
- 如果Miles不想和我在一起，
I don't want to be around him!
我也不想和他在一起！
I'm gonna break up with him!
我要和他分手！
Will you come with me?
你能陪我去吗？
- Of course I will.
- 当然可以。
Yeah, let's hold that as a backup plan.
是的，让我们把这个作为备用计划。
♪♪
- Can you smell that, boys?
- 你们能闻到吗，男孩们？
That's the smell of sweaty men and churros.
那是汗流浃背的男人和炸玉米饼的味道。
- Do you see it now, Miles?
你现在看到了吗，迈尔斯？
- Ugh, Ms. Purr-fect.
呃，完美小姐。
A cat is the last thing I want to see right now.
我现在最不想看到的就是一只猫。
You know, I was finally starting to forget
你知道吗，我终于开始忘记
about Mae's cat, Debbie.
关于梅的猫，黛比。
- What do you have against Debbie?
你为什么不喜欢黛比？
- Oh, I don't know. Just all the things
哦，我不知道。只是我
I've been talking about all day.
一整天都在谈论的所有事情。
- So when you said she scares you, you meant Debbie?
所以当你说她吓到你时，你指的是黛比？
- Yeah.
是的。
- So when you said you didn't like her at all,
- 所以当你说你一点都不喜欢她时，
you meant Debbie?
你指的是Debbie？
- Yeah, who else would I mean?
- 是的，我还能指谁？
- Nobody. - Beats me.
- 没人。 - 我也不知道。
- Definitely not Mae.
- 绝对不是Mae。
- Oh, there's our seats.
- 哦，那是我们的座位。
Time to dude up and suit up.
该打扮得体了。
You think that hurts? Waaaah!
你觉得这很痛吗？哇！
[all cheering]
[所有人欢呼]
- We really messed up.
- 我们真的搞砸了。
We need to call Dawn and tell her before--
我们需要给Dawn打电话，告诉她之前--
[rock music]
[cheers and applause]
- Um, what's going on?
呃，发生什么事了？
- Look. It's the Three Mask-eteers.
看，是三位蒙面斗士。
Get ready to get rattled!
准备好被震撼吧！
[rattling]
- We have our masks on.
我们已经戴上面具了。
They must think we're the actual Three Mask-eteers.
他们一定以为我们是真正的三位蒙面斗士。
- You think?
你这么认为？
- Um, Mr. Wrestler sirs...
嗯，摔跤先生们...
and madam,
还有女士，
there seems to be a little misunderstanding.
这里似乎有点误会。
- We're not the actual Mask-eteers.
我们不是真正的三面具侠。
- Totally not.
绝对不是。
- I may be a big baby, but I'm no dummy.
我可能是个大宝宝，但我不是傻瓜。
- You're about to get cat scratch fever.
你马上就要得猫抓热了。
[hisses] - Get ready to gingi-fight-us!
准备好进行金吉战斗吧！
- Ah, go! Go, go, go!
啊，快！快，快，快！
[yells] - [gasps]
（大喊）-（喘气）
- Now do you want to do this the easy way
- 你想用简单的方式来做这件事吗？
or the hard way?
- 还是困难的方式？
- What's the easy way?
- 简单的方式是什么？
- We pick you up by the head, we spin you around,
- 我们抓住你的头，把你转几圈，
and we throw you into the ring!
- 然后把你扔进擂台！
- And what's the hard way?
- 那困难的方式呢？
- Making me angry by asking me what the easy way was first!
- 先问我简单的方式是什么，这让我很生气！
[together] Get in the ring!
[一起] 进擂台！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
[all cheering]
[所有人欢呼]
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
Keep them busy while I call Dawn.
拖住他们，我打电话给Dawn。
- Oh, yeah. Sure. That'll be easy!
- 哦，对。当然。那会很容易！
- Waaah!
- 哇！
- You know what? I won the VR wrestling match.
- 你知道吗？我赢了VR摔跤比赛。
I think I can take 'em. - Wha--
我觉得我能对付他们。 - 什么--
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[yelling]
[大喊]
Oh, no. [grunts]
哦，不。 [咕哝]
[strained] I guess I can't take 'em.
[吃力地] 我想我打不过他们。
- Where are the guys?
- 那些家伙去哪儿了？
- I don't know, but they're missing all the action!
- 我不知道，但他们错过了所有精彩的部分！
- Nicky, catch this!
- 尼基，接住这个！
- Oh no! Looks like your phone fell in the litter box.
- 哦不！看来你的手机掉进猫砂盆里了。
- Bad kitty!
- 坏猫咪！
- Time to put you in a lock-a-bye cradle hold.
- 是时候把你放进摇篮式抱抱了。
- Bad baby!
- 坏宝宝！
If by any chance you plan on throwing me,
如果你们打算扔我，
could you possibly throw me in that direction?
能不能朝那个方向扔？
- Good night, moon! - [screaming]
- 晚安，月亮！ - [尖叫]
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- Hey, guys. It's me, Nicky!
嘿，伙计们。是我，Nicky！
There's something I need to explain to you!
有件事我需要向你们解释！
- [grunting]
[咕哝声]
What we overheard Miles say earlier wasn't about Mae,
我们之前无意中听到Miles说的话，不是关于Mae的，
it was about...Debbie!
而是关于...Debbie的！
- Debbie was the one Miles doesn't want to be around.
Debbie才是Miles不想待在身边的人。
He really doesn't like your cat!
他真的很不喜欢你的猫！
[thudding, all groan]
[砰砰声，所有人呻吟]
- [chuckles] Well, that's a relief.
[轻笑] 嗯，这倒是让人松了口气。
At least we know Miles doesn't want to break up with you.
至少我们知道Miles不想和你分手。
Just your cat.
只是你的猫。
- Just my cat?
- 只是我的猫？
You don't like Debbie? My Debbie?
你不喜欢Debbie？我的Debbie？
- Uh-oh.
- 哦哦。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[all groaning]
[所有人呻吟]
- I'm sorry about all this, Mae.
- 我很抱歉这一切，Mae。
I really need to learn how to--
我真的需要学会如何——
- Stay out of other people's business?
- 不插手别人的事？
Communicate better? Buy your dad a calendar?
更好地沟通？给你爸爸买个日历？
- Yes, all of those.
- 是的，所有这些。
So are you and Miles gonna be okay?
那么你和Miles会没事的吗？
- Yeah, I can't stay mad at that big ol' softy.
- 是的，我无法对那个大块头心软的家伙生气太久。
- [groans] Sorry, Miles.
- [呻吟] 对不起，Miles。
This is all our fault.
这都是我们的错。
- We probably should've told you about Mae earlier.
- 我们可能应该早点告诉你关于Mae的事情。
- We just didn't want to ruin dude night.
- 我们只是不想毁了哥们之夜。
- Are you kidding? Best dude night ever!
- 你在开玩笑吗？这是有史以来最好的哥们之夜！
[cheers and applause, boys yelling]
[欢呼和掌声，男孩们大喊]
- [laughing] - Yeah!
- [笑] - 是啊！
[all cheering]
[全体欢呼]
[all exclaiming and cheering]
[全体惊叹和欢呼]
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪